followupsellingsystems.com 2010-04-19

# Privacy

**OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

FollowUpSellingSystems.com is committed to protecting the privacy of our online visitors.

We collect information from online visitors who ask to be on our newsletter mailing list and/or receive periodic email announcements.

Anyone who wishes can choose to be removed from our mailing list at any time.

In addition, online visitors who wish to purchase a membership through our Web site must provide their name, email address, mailing address, phone number, and credit card number and expiration date. All credit card transactions occur over a secure connection.

We do not store credit card numbers on our servers and use third party services for payment processing and shopping cart services.

All online visitor data collected by FollowUpSellingSystems.com is protected against unauthorized access.

We will not sell, trade, or give your personal information to other companies or organizations.

We use Aweber for our email newsletter. Aweber's email privacy policy can be viewed [here](http://www.aweber.com/privacy.htm?id=99).

**Children's Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems. CharliePage.com encourages parents to go online with their kids.

Here are a few tips to help make a child's online experience safer:

Teach kids never to give personal information, unless supervised by a parent or responsible adult. Includes name, address, phone, school, etc.

Know the sites your kids are visiting and which sites are appropriate.

Look for Web site privacy policies. Know how your child's information is treated.

Check out the FTC's site

_[http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/edcams/kidzprivacy/index.html](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/edcams/kidzprivacy/index.htmlf)_  for more tips on protecting children's privacy online.

**Contacting Us**

We can be reached via our support center. [Click here to access our support center.](http://www.charliepagesupport.com/)

FollowUpSellingSystems.com

### No Spam Policy  
  
We do not promote any form of SPAM or sending of email to ANYONE who has not requested information from you.

We do not suggest BUYING MAILING LISTS or performing BULK EMAILING

The bottom line is simple, if you are not mailing to an opt-in list (people who expressly request your information) you are sending spam.

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of people's email addresses and are against the use of UCE (Unsolicited Commercial Email) or spamming including newsgroup mailing.

Please report your issue with us and we will investigate your concerns forthwith.

If you have any questions please contact Charlie Page using the link in the "Contacting Us" section above.
